codesdope.com 2018-12-17

# Privacy Policy for codesdope

* * *

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### Personal information

* * *

#### What personal information do we collect from the people who visit our blog, website or app?

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

#### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

#### How do we use your information?

We do not sell your personal information to others. We use this personally identifiable information to register you to access our services.  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register in the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

#### Disclosure of information

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, or when we believe that disclosure doing so in the Company's interest, and to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.  
Should the company have its assets sold to or merged with another business entity, we reserve the right to transfer the information we receive from this website including your personally identifiable information to a successor as a result of any such corporate reorganization.

#### Retention of information

We will keep personally identifiable Information of our users for as long as they are registered subscribers or users of our products and services, and as permitted by law.

#### What informations are publicly displayed?

Informations like username, name, school, about yourself and your social profiles (like Facebook profile URL, Github profile URL, Twitter profile URL, Linkedin profile URL, Google+ profile URL, etc.) are publicly displayed if you post something on the website.

You can change your personal information: 

  * By logging in to your account

### Cookies

* * *

#### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, they are used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We also use cookies to understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.   
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly. 

#### Social Website Cookies

Cookies are used by social websites (like Facebook and Twitter) so you can easily Like or share our content with the sharing buttons on our site.  
The privacy implications on this will vary from the different social websites and are dependent on the privacy settings you have chosen on these networks. 

#### Visitor Statistics Cookies

We use cookies to compile visitor statistics such as how many people have visited our website, what type of technology they are using (e.g. Mac or Windows which helps to identify when our site isn't working as it should for particular technologies), how long they spend on the site, what page they look at etc.  
This helps us to continuously improve our website. These analytics programs also tell us how people reached this site (e.g. from a search engine) and whether they have been here before helping us to put more money into developing our services for you instead of marketing spend.  
We use:  
Google Analytics - [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/) owned by Google. 

#### Advertising Cookies

Cookies are widely used in online advertising. Neither us, advertisers or our advertising partners can gain personally identifiable information from these cookies. 

You can learn more about online advertising, or opt-out of almost all advertising cookies at [https://www.youronlinechoices.com](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/). 

We use:  

  * Google Adsense [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) owned by Google.
  * Double Click [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) owned by Google.
  * appnexus.com
  * districtm.io
  * freewheel.tv
  * adtech.com
  * coxmt.com
  * Openx.com
  * indexexchange.com
  * sonobi.com
  * sovrn.com
  * lijit.com
  * openx.com
  * pubmatic.com
  * contextweb.com
  * gumgum.com
  * 33across.com
  * Advertising.com
  * aolcloud.net
  * bidtellect.com
  * criteo.com
  * lkqd.com
  * lkqd.net
  * outbrain.com
  * revcontent.com
  * rhythmone.com
  * smaato.com
  * spotx.tv
  * spotxchange.com
  * springserve.com
  * sekindo.com
  * adform.com
  * improvedigital.com
  * smartclip.net
  * loopme.com
  * aps.amazon.com
  * rubiconproject.com
  * yldbt.com
  * lockerdome.com

Opting out of advertising cookies will not disable ads, they will just no longer be tailored to you. 

### Miscellaneous

* * *

#### Links to other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. The users need to take notice of the fact that the linked websites are governed by their own privacy policies and we disclaim any responsibility arising out of your actions on the linked website. We advise users to go through the privacy policy of the linked website and their terms and conditions before sharing any information to these websites. 

#### You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below or visit our contact us page.   
help@codesdope.com
